momentville.com 2009-11-03

# MomentVille Privacy Policy | Free Wedding Websites

##  Privacy Policy : MomentVille Vendor Directory 

Date of Last Revision: Aug 1, 2008. 

Overview 

MomentVille is serious about protecting your privacy. The following privacy policy details how we will and will not use your personal information. 

###  Summary (Plain English) 

  * We collect information about you that you volunteer. 
  * We also collect some information about you that is given during your interactions with us (like your ip address) 
  * We use this information to make our service to you better, including targeting information and ads to you that you will hopefully find useful! 
  * We will not give your information to other companies. We are opposed to spam. 
  * We may occasionally email you information about your account, MomentVille, or special offers. For instance, if you have an RSVP you may want to get updates on who has RSVPed. 
  * Information you post is accessible to search engines and others on the internet. 

###  What Information We Collect 

When you visit MomentVille you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site. 

To create an account and start making a MomentVille website, you need to submit a valid email address and create a password. From time-to-time we will use your email address to communicate with you about your account, about MomentVille, and about special offers. Additional use of this address is limited to the uses listed below in "Information Sharing and Disclosure." 

You post user content on the site at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that content you post on the site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of content you have posted may remain viewable if other users have copied or stored it. 

###  Cookies 

MomentVille uses cookies to aid navigation and improve your experience while using the site. Cookies are small files stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser. We never save personal information such as passwords or credit card numbers in the cookies. If your browser it set to not use cookies, you will not be able to do perform any actions that require login. You will be able to view public Momentville websites. 

###  Information Sharing and Disclosure 

MomentVille will never rent, sell, or share your email, physical address or other personal information to a third party, except in the following circumstances: 

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MomentVille's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law. 
  * If MomentVille becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

###  Use Of Information 

Information posted by individuals on the on MomentVille websites is public and visible to anyone visiting those pages. 

MomentVille may contain images, or other embedded objects from other web sites. These other sites maintain their own policies regarding cookies and the collection and use of personal information. It is up to you to review those policies yourself. 

###  Third-Party Advertising Companies 

MomentVille will use information you have provided so that we may provide helpful advertisements that you will find useful. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our site. Our system and the third-party advertising technology uses information derived from your visits to our site and from information you have volunteered. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on our site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed on your computer. MomentVille does not provide any personally identifiable information to third-party advertising companies. 

###  Changes to this Policy 

MomentVille may update or modify this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

###  Additional Questions or Concerns 

For any further questions about our privacy policy, please contact us by email at [ privacy@momentville.com ](mailto:privacy@momentville.com)
